

#### **COMPUTER ENGINEER**



## Personal Information

linkedin.com/in/s%C3%BCphan-yakut-81a839220
yakutsuphan@gmail.com
+905541749144
https://github.com/0Suphan0
SSK Blokları Serpmeleri 106/11,Ankara, Türkiye
Driving Licence-B

## About Me

I graduated from Gazi University with a degree in Computer Science and Engineering. Throughout my academic journey, I have successfully completed various projects in web development, mobile app development, and game development. Proficient in the Object-Oriented Programming paradigm, I have demonstrated my skills in crafting applications using .Net, Java, and Flutter (Dart). You can explore the projects I've worked on by visiting my GitHub repository.

## Work Experience



Flutter Developer Intern Vakıf Global Bilişim ve Teknoloji

Jun 2022 to August 2022 (3 months)

I developed a mobile application using Flutter, designed to facilitate task assignment and monitoring in alignment with the System and Network team's annual maintenance and exercise plan requirements.



# Software Engineer TUALCOM Elektronik A.Ş

March 2023 to August 2023

- Developing mobile application with Flutter.
  - 1. Sending and receiving Broadcast UDP packages
  - 2. Dart:10 library
  - 3. Chat App
- Developing desktop application with Java (Eclipse RCP)
  - 1. SWT Widgets
  - 2. Bug-Fixing and Testing
- SVN

#### Education



Süleyman Demirel Anatolian High School (85) January 2015 - June 2018

Gazi University( September 2018 - 2024 (expected graduation date) ) Computer Science And Engineering

OOP, Data Structures, Algorithms, Database Management Systems, Programming

### **Technical Skills**

Programming Languages:, Flutter (Dart), Java, Net CORE,

Javascript, PostgreSQL, MySQL

Libraries Tools and Frameworks: Angular, RCP, Swing, Unity

Languages: Turkish(Native Language), English(Intermediate),

German(Beginner)

Soft Skills: Team Communication, Leadership, Endurance